Lucas Torres

Montreal (514)442-2257 torresjuanlucas@gmail.com http://lucastorres.ipd10.com/



OBJECTIVE

I am looking for an internship or a job opportunity as a Web Developer. I would like a friendly environment, where I can practice and further develop the practical skills acquired during my AEC Internet Programming & Development program at John Abbott College. I am a creative person; with my many years of data entry specialist and as a salesman I am ready to offer loyalty, dedication and hard work to my employer.

SKILLS / TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML5, CCS3, JavaScript, PHP, Bootstrap, XML, jQuery, Bulma
- MySQL, Access, MS SQL Server
- Micro-framework PHP Slim, Twig,
- C#, .Net, WPF, XAML
- Java, Enterprise Java Beans
- NetBeans, Visual Studio Community, Sublime
- Dream Weaver CS6
- GitHub, Bitbucket, Source Tree, XAMPP, Apache
- Scrum, Trello
- Ability to interact with the stakeholders and understand user needs
- Autonomy to find solutions
- Strong communication, interpersonal, and presentation skills
- Strong troubleshooting and problem solving skills with an analytical mindset
- Fast learner with strong time management and multi-tasking skills
- More than ten years of user support experience

EDUCATION

AEC Internet Programming and Development at John Abbott CEGEP/College	03/2017 - 02/2018
WORK EXPERIENCE	
SeCe apparel ltd. Assistant manager & Data entry specialist	02/2014 - 03/2017
Implement workflow strategies and supervise the employees, control the electronic data flow between companies and manage the deliveries via EDI implementing Momentis software and EDIGateway system.	
Amerella of Canada ltd. Assistant manager & Data entry specialist	08/2003 - 02/2013

Implement workflow strategies and supervise the employees, control the electronic data flow between companies and manage the deliveries via EDI implementing Momentis software and EDIGateway system.

LANGUAGES

English, French, Spanish.

AVAILABILITY

Up to February 1st, 2017 available part-time. Starting February 1st, 2017, available full-time.